sudoku.name 2006-06-15

# Sudoku.name Privacy policy

www.sudoku.name respects the privacy concerns of visitors to our site www.sudoku.name. We do not sell or disclose your email address or other information about you. We may log IP addresses to prevent abuse of our website and newsletters. www.sudoku.name Limited may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with www.sudoku.name's property, visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. 

What personal information is collected? 

Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. www.sudoku.name only collects personal information from our online visitors on a voluntary basis. We do not require personal information to obtain access to any of our sites; however, you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

What about cookies? 

Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within web sites. Certain of our sites use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and for other purposes. For example, certain of our sites use “cookies” or other methods to monitor website usage. We collect information on what games are played, how much time is spent playing the games and which ads or links are clicked. We may link cookie information to personal information. 

Certain of our sites use an outside ad company to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and www.sudoku.name does not have access to this information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our sites will not function properly if you do so. 

Third Party Sites 

If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, or an Ad company, you will leave the www.sudoku.name site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as www.sudoku.name. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to an www.sudoku.name site, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information. 

WWW.SUDOKU.NAME Newsletter/Email Policy 

We strive to keep our customers happy by providing them with an easy to use system for joining and unjoing our lists. Our newsletters have an easy to use system with alternative methods of unjoing to ensure that you can easily be removed from our lists. This is done automatically or if need be, manually by our help department. www.sudoku.name, will use it's email list for announcing new Sudoku companies and for customer relationship. 

1\. We don't sell our email lists. 

2\. We don't loan our email lists. 

3\. We don't let other companies use our email lists. 

4\. We don't disclose our email addresses to anyone else. 

The personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and events of interest, by mail, or directly through our site. 

Safeguarding Your Personal Information 

We will only collect and use personal information in accordance with this privacy policy to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, accuracy and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any personal information will provide sufficient protection of that information. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the www.sudoku.name Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use www.sudoku.name site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Also, if there is a substantive change in the way that we use your personal information, we will notify you via e-mail of the relevant changes. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Online Privacy Policy.
